Cinderella
Cinderella's Sister
Moon Geun Young
Cheon Jeong Myeong
Seo Woo
Taecyeon
Lee Mi Sook
Kim Gap Soo
Cinderella's Sister
Won't you let go?
Come on, Kang Sook.
Ms. Kang Sook. Ms. Kang Sook.
Episode 1
Won't you let go?
Didn't I say I would stay over? Please forgive me just this once.
Remove your hands, you bastard.
What can I do huh?
I will do all that you say. Just say it.
Did you make me like this because you will do what I say?
That's not what I did.
Alcohol...
I don't want to hear it, you bastard. Move your face!
So, didn't I say don't come near me when I drink?
What can I do, this body is so pretty.
Go away!
Did you just throw that? Did you just throw that at me?
- Nui ( Sister)
- Shut your mouth!
Because of your blabbering
Nui, aren't you going to give me something to eat?
- Why are you eating this up all by yourself?
- Don't you hear that?
= Stop!
- Where are you going do you want to die?
Move!
I don't know when I'll get to eat food at a table again like this.
I have to eat as if it's my last. Don't talk to me.
Are you going to leave?
It's all your fault, you woman.
Nui, if you're going to leave then this is my final meal.
There won't be anyone to cook for me once you leave.
You want to die?
You want to kill me? Go ahead and kill me!
I'll kill you. You die, you die...
You made this happen! It's all your fault.
You're just asking to die, aren't you?
Kill me! Go ahead and kill me then!
Listen carefully to what I have to say.
It doesn't matter where you end up or where you live,
I'll find you and take care of you for the rest of your life.
Believe what I say.
No! Eun Jo!
Say you are sorry!
What are you doing, you bitch?
Have you gone crazy?
Song Eun Jo is Han Jeong Woo's girl forever.
Nui, where are you going?
Nui!
Please.
- Please, please. Please, wait.
- No!
Hey, this is all ripped up. How can I run away looking like this? I must get changed.
Do you think this is the time to worry about that? Hurry up and follow me!
Kang Sook!
Hurry up, let's go.
Hurry up.
Don't go.
Come this way immediately.
Let's hurry up.
Don't go. Don't go!
Don't go.
Kang Sook!
Noona, don't get caught... Goodbye!
Kang Sook, I'm sorry.
Kang Sook.
You can't.
If I catch you two, you're dead.
Noona. Eat well and stay healthy!
Ahjussi. Do you want to kill me?
If you're going to kill me, will you wait until I finish eating?
We don't even have a plan. No plan! Without any money in our pockets, what are we going to do?
Have we ever had any money before? We've never had money every time we ran away...
We have nowhere to go. What's the point of getting on the train? There's nowhere to get off.
Anywhere! As long as it's not here!
You make no sense. No sense at all.
Ahjussi, take us back where you picked us up.
Just go on to the train station, Ahjussi.
Ahjussi, if you want to get your fare, go back.
We can't miss the 4.30 train. Hurry up, Ahjussi!
- You brat!
- Do you really want to go back after getting beaten up so much?
You said there was nothing more to take from him!
Why are you crawling back to that man whom you can't get anything from to just get beaten until your back is bruised?
Why are you screaming at me when you don't know a thing, you little wretch!
Don't cuss at me!
- Ahjussi!
Get out. I can't drive because you're too noisy.
Both of you get out.
Ahjussi, go back to where we weren before.
Really! This crazy woman!
Mom, Is this what you really want?
If this is what you wanted to get from him, I took it so we can just go now.
Ahjussi, hurry up and take us to the train station, what are you doing?
If we miss our train, are you going to be responsible for it and take us? Hurry up to the train station!
Consider this to be your fate in life.
You were about to give it to Ajumma Kang Sook anyway.
You thought she would grab it and run away. So that's why you hid it.
Bring Dae Bong to me.
Dae... Dae Bong? What do you want with that gangster?
Do you want a beating?
No. I don't.
Myeongbong Station
Look here. What time does that train arrive at the next station?
It arrives at 5.00 PM.
- Can we get there by that time?
- We can.
Let's go.
How could you pack this way?
What's all this?
Are we going to a fashion show?
This is the best one you packed but to wear this,
I have to redo my hair and retouch my make up.
Is there a beauty salon on this train?
Noona, I thought I might get beaten to death, so I went to get Dae Bong.
Don't let him catch you and stay safe.
If you ever get caught by him, your bones won't be left.
I won't get caught. Hang up.
Who asked you to do this, you bad girl?
Don't you dare to curse. It makes you sound uneducated.
You are a thief!
When she is in a good mood, she cusses.
If she is in a bad mood also, she cusses.
Thank you.
She's a mother but that's how she lives. Please understand.
She does far worse things like they are nothing.
Do you think you'd like to have a mother like her?
Mom! Mom!
- Move. Get out of the way!
- Why?
- Get out of the way!
- What's wrong with them?
My mom's had more than a million men.
Before she could give me father number 1000...
I've decided to abandon her.
Mum. Quickly, run.
Over there!
But in the end, it became like this.
Darn it...
Hey, get out of the way!
Away.
Aigoo, get the heck out the way, wench.
You can just cut ahead!
How can I go first with these clothes? I mean it's silk!
Is that important right now?
Stop, punks.
She's over there.
Move out of the way.
Ah, what do we do now?
Oh, what should we do?
Goo Hyo Sun
Ms. Song Kang Sook. Open the door!
Daeseong True Wine Makers
Stop, stop, stop.
Why didn't you pick up your phone? I have to transfer schools right away.
I don't know what it's about, but if you're here at this time it means you've skipped class.
If I hear the reason and it's nothing big, I'll scold you.
That woman said she'd come and find me at my school soon but the ring has disappeared, the ring, I tell you.
Hello, good work.
Oh, you came?
During the Korean class, when I saw the teacher wearing her ring, the memory came back to me.
When I was coming back from the class trip, I definitely had it on.
But after that I haven't seen it.
I even went home.
I can't find it no matter what.
What do I do?
- Hello from Daeseong True Wine Makers.
- Oh, you're here?
I'm in really big trouble.
If I say I've lost the ring, the kid certainly looked like someone who'd maul my face.
What am I going to do?
My president says he will come by the day after tomorrow.
Please give our regards to your president as well.
Yes, you've worked hard.
Yes, sir. Thank you.
In any case, I think I need to transfer schools.
Where should I go?
Should I go far away to some place like Seoul?
The MP3 you lost the last time, you found it at the president's library after a week, right?
So what?
The keepsake T-shirt you bought at H.O.T.'s last concert,
didn't you say you found the housekeeper grandma using it as a rag after half a year?
Grandma is really mean.
I mean, how can she use my Oppa Kangta as a rag?
You've also lost the watch the president bought you as a commencement present, right?
How did you know?
I know since you left it in my room.
How much was I looking for that?
Is there anything you've lost forever?
I'm asking if within the things you've lost at home, is there something you've never been able to find?
There wasn't.
Then it's fine.
It hurts.
Go in quickly.
I am in big trouble wasting time because of you.
I have two more places I have to go to.
Bro.
You're mine.
What?
If you say the moon is rectangular, then I think it is rectangular.
If you say salt is sweet and sugar is salty,
I am going to gulp down salt water and spew out sugar water.
Since you say I can find the ring, it feels like it's never been lost.
Did I lose a ring?
Why do you talk so much you little thing?
I'm busy.
If I get fired because I can't finish my work while helping you, will you take responsibility?
Since you're mine, you can't get married to anyone. Okay?
I don't want even Jeon Do Yeon or Go So Young.
Oppa, Bye.
What is that?
I should have snuck in during the recess.
10th Grade - Homeroom No. 4
Goo Hyo Seon
It must be you.
At my call you
Come quickly.
It's so horrible that I could die.
How could you leave me here alone and go off by yourself?
How could you do that?
If I had left with you, that human would have thought we were running away again and would have followed me.
I will find the ring, take care of it and come straight back for you.
Finish it off? What and how are you going to finish it off?
You don't need to know.
Mom.
Ajumma!
Oh, are you all done?
Where is your house?
I mean ...
What can I do about it?
But, why did you come Ajumma?
I thought that kid Song Eun Jo would come.
She's my daughter.
But, do we have to go for a while?
We're almost there.
Back then, how did it go with those bad guys?
The men that came to find you in the bathrooms? Did the police lock them up?
Did you give them a taste of the prison food?
If it's far, let's take a taxi.
We're almost there. It's just over there.
My dad says
men who bother women are the pettiest and worst kind of human beings in the world.
I'll pay the taxi fare. Let's take a taxi, yeah?
But it's just right over there.
You keep saying it's right here, right there.
Child, Hyo Seon!
Hyo Seon!
What a ruckus! The president is fuming.
He has all the staff at home on their knees.
He hasn't even allowed any food since lunch time.
From lunch until now?
What to do?
Oh my, hey you. Where are you going?
She really...
- It's this way.
- Hurry.
I can't sell this kind of alcohol.
How can you call this wine?
Boss, please don't do this.
This kid.
If you put in rice, yeast and water and mix them up, does that just make rice wine?
Is anything with two eyes and a nose a human being?
Whether it is angry or crestfallen, you must check the temperature and humidity frequently
and you must tend to it and nurse it, I told you.
Why did you mindessly neglect it and create this craziness?
This isn't alcohol! This is sewage!
Dad!
Dad, Dad.
Who brought her in here?!
Dad, stop it.
I asked who brought her here? Did you, Grannies?
Dad, Ahjussis... their knees must be hurting.
You go home.
Dad.
Among those kneeling men,
half of them are my friends' dads.
Dad.
I don't want to even see your faces. All of you get lost.
Dad...
Dad.
Mr, are you okay?
Are you okay?
Ahjussi...
Our president, when his wife was alive, he was not that nasty.
All of you must be hungry. Hurry to the dining room.
Grandma, did the mother here pass away?
When Hyo Seon was 8 years old.
But, who are you?
I am sorry.
Ajumma, I forgot.
No, it's fine. I see that this was an important matter.
Yes. Quickly, come to my house with me.
Okay. Is your house far?
It can be far, let's go slowly.
Far? It really is just over there.
Over there.
Is that place really...
It was really close then.
Yes.
Come along.
Just a moment.
I'll be right back.
Where did it go? Where did it go? Where did it go?
Yes, like that.
That's right.
You seem to have a lot of work.
Should I help you a little bit?
But who are you?
I... never lost it.
There's nothing that I've lost forever.
Because I'm opening mom's stuff for the first time in a long time,
I don't think it will be in here.
Bible
The bag I took to the class trip!
Where was it?
Where did it go?
Aigoo, what to do?
- Aigoo, what to do?
- Missus, you sure are strange.
Why get in the way of the water being thrown away?
I'm really sorry.
I was trying to help you...
It's okay. I can just dry it off.
It does smell a bit fishy but,
the fish smell is very potent.
What's wrong, Ajumma?
You said these are your late mother's clothes, so I don't know if it's okay for me to be wearing these.
I'll only wear these until my clothes are dry.
What's wrong?
You're... really pretty.
Right, thank you.
Ahjumma, you resemble Hwang Shin Hye (doll-like type).
Omo, kid, how can that be? I resemble Jeong Yoon Hee (voluptuous type).
My mom looked like Hwang Shin Hye too.
Right, I often hear that I look like Hwang Shin Hye, too.
Omo, child,
What's wrong?
What is?
Did I do something wrong?
The clothes really suit you well.
Right, thank you.
The clothes really do suit you well.
Why are you crying so much?
I don't know.
My tears just keep coming out.
Don't cry, hm? Don't cry.
Don't cry.
Don't cry...
Please do it again.
Hm?
Please do this for me.
Please wait here for a moment.
Okay, thank you.
Go in, Ajumma.
Who is she?
Uncle, have you not seen my travel bag?
Huh?
My travel bag.
What Oppa Gi Hoon bought me, the one with green plaids, haven't you seen it?
Oh, that one! You took it to the attic the last time.
Shall I find it for you?
No, lock it up.
Pardon?
Lock it up. Hide it thoroughly, Uncle.
What? What are you saying right now?
Are you saying the wine release might be put off to fall?
Look here, look here, it has to be marketed by summer no matter what.
Do you know how much your monthly pay is?
Do you want me to show what happens if you try to take other people's money for nothing?
This won't do.
Forget about going home and wait right there. I will be at the lab straight away.
Hang up.
I'm sorry.
I was waiting until you finished your phone call.
Who...?
Hyo Seon...
Hyo Seon?
But, what's the problem..?
For a person she didn't know,
because she agreed to keep a thing without knowing anything about it,
I heard that you scolded her very much.
That... Hyo Seon
said from some girl of the same age as Hyo Seon...
Yes, I am that child's mother.
We had a situation, but its not a bad object.
If you don't believe me, there's nothing I can do about it.
Anyway, I'm sorry.
Also, I know these words might be a bit surprising on our first meeting but
I have a favour to ask you.
Of course, there's nothing I can do if you reject me
I heard that the bag with the item I left to your daughter was loaned to a friend who lives far away.
It will take some time before she finds it.
I have nowhere else to run.
While I'm waiting, could I not work here?
Kitchen work or any other work will be fine.
I know how ridiculous my words may seem...
I told you no.
I am here.
I am here, so there's no reason my mom wouldn't come.
She says the business is just taking longer.
Do you trust your mom?
What did you say?
Because you are here, do you think your mom
will return here no matter what because of you...
Do you believe that?
Of course.
Your mom,
has she never abandoned you?
She hasn't.
She would never.
Then, that's fine.
What are you doing right now?!
Are you not leaving?
Jeong Woo!
Jeong Woo!!!
I can't do this, lose some fat!
Your call could not be connected...
Once connected to the voice mailbox, you will be charged.
Hyo Seon is home!
Where is she?
Oppa!
You came?
I'm hurt.
I got hurt..
All done.
I want to see it.
I am going to keep it.
Daeseong True Wine Makers
Seeing that your lights are on...
What...
Today is Hyo Sun's painting competition, so I promised to make her a lunch box.
But I didn't have time to go grocery shopping. Can you give me the directions?
It's far.
It's okay. I can just walk there slowly.
I can go by myself though...
Oh, I'm scared.
Aigoo, what are you doing?
What's wrong?
Oppa.
Uncle...
gave Ajumma Song Kang Sook the ring.
Thank you for everything. - Song Kang Sook.
The last train is in thirty minutes and the last bus is in an hour.
I can just go to the train station and you can go to the bus station.
I don't want to hear it so get out.
Hyo Seon can't handle the situation right now.
She's always like that when a guest leaves.
I'll escort her for now.
What's with you, punk?
Hyo Seon has been happy as if she has become a seven year old kid lately.
She's a seven year old kid separated from her Mom..
Be quiet and don't do anything.
How can she leave without saying anything?
How can a person do that? Why would you go look for a person who decided to do that?
No matter what you do, I'm going to the train station.
Tell me I'll see her again.
It'll work out the way you say it will.
Tell me she's coming. Quickly!
Quickly tell me that she's coming.
What was it...
Even though you knew the kid was kidding around and hid it, why are you pretending not to know?
What was the purpose?
Since you've been here because of this the whole time, now that you have it back, you can take it and leave then.
I want to go my way, but I can't do that, Goo Dae Seong.
You're leaving?
How can you leave like this?
You got attached to the kid. How can you...?
I've imposed on you a lot.
I have left Hyo Seon's mom's clothes all mended.
The kid's crying.
My daughter is probably crying right now too.
You can just bring your child here then.
The man I lived with is holding onto my child.
It won't be easy to bring her here.
I told you I'll bring her here. I will.
Is this solely because of Hyo Seon?
Are you only telling me to stay here because of Hyo Seon?
Give me rice! I only ate kimchi so I'm hungry.
Move it.
Still, you don't have a single thing to worry about.
I'll take responsibility for you.
Get lost.
Don't they say, though, a widower best knows a widow's circumstances?
What? My mom left me with that Hairball and ran away.
Your mom, too, done left you with that Hairball
and done ran away, no?
So my mom ran away?
Yes.
Abandoning me?
Yes!
Are you sure?
Why do you keep making me say the same thing?
Long live.
Your mom isn't even here. Where are you going?
To run away.
By yourself?
Because I'm by myself.
Because I'm alone, I'm running away.
If I don't have my mom, I can be happy.
That's not right.
What are you doing?
I can't send you alone.
What?
Didn't I say I can't send you off alone? Quickly unpack your things.
Are you not going to let go?
I'll let go...
Look here. I've done all that I can.
I made a lot of food, and I prepared enough kimchi for the two of you to eat for a few months.
I did all the laundry and cleaning.
I also filled up the fridge with a lot of alcohol so you can drown in alcohol for three months.
That's all then, right?
I don't have any debt to you.
If you think of the ring as debt...
then find my Mom and get it from her.
Not me.
Nui, nui!
Nui!
If you follow me, you're dead.
Nui ...
Song Eun Joo, student?
While living, there's stuff one must and must not do.
I try to be patient.
Who does he think I am?
But what's the reason for asking me especially to do this?
Lean your back on the back rest and go comfortably. You look uncomfortable.
Leave your bag next to you. If you're sleepy, you can sleep comfortably.
I want to go to the restroom
Huh?
Restroom.
Ah, look at this.
Women's restroom
Wow, really. Isn't she pulling out everything from her stomach?
How long ago did she go in?
I won't stop.
Even if I have to spend the future searching for food in trash cans
I will never go to my mom Song Kang Sook
in the house of whatever good-for-nothing man
whom that woman grabbed the ankle of,
Just a moment!
Wait a minute and stop for a moment!
Ah! Let go!
Your mother won't just follow you easily.
She warned me and asked me to take you carefully, saying you might run away. I guess she was right.
Do you have somewhere to go? Do you have money?
Are you thinking when you go somewhere on your last day, there's nothing I won't do to survive?
That's... not easy.
Even if you go somewhere, they won't accept you as a minor.
Even if you work to death you don't know whether you will make a lot of money or not.
The expenses are not cheap.
It'll change a bit as soon as you turn 20, so just endure it for a little bit.
How about leaving home once you turn 20?
Huh?
It's weird. It's really weird,
Even if he says the moon is rectangular, I want to believe him.
I must be possessed by a ghost.
I should've just jumped out of the train then and there!
Be quiet.
This time, how far will we go?
If we get thrown out of here again or runaway, it's one or the other.
How fare are we going to go this time? 3 months? 4 months?
I told you this person is not like that!
It's not like that?! What's not like that?!
Looking from the back, what's the difference between this man and any other man?
Mom, just please!
Let's not get attached to men who aren't human just to eat a meal, huh?
Just you and I can somehow survive.
Are you not going to lower your voice?!
I don't want to! I won't do it. Mom, you can just do it alone.
Who am I doing this for!
Lies! The lies that you do it for me,
I need to sew your lips together in order not to hear you!
What?
Let go!
Come here! Follow me!
- Come.
- Let me go!
-Let me go!
-Come here.
Let go!
-This wench, this wench!
-Don't do this.
You don't realize all the effort I have put in to survive.
You're my daughter and what did you say? You'll sew my lips together?
Who did I do all of this for?
Don't say it's for me! Mom, do you live for me?!
A mom that lived for me...
Is that why you abandoned me?
What? Abandon?
When did I abandon you?
Since I gave birth to you without your father, I've never once thought of abandoning you!
Even If I knew because of you my future was doomed,
I've never once thought of abandoning you!
You left me alone at that house!
With that creepy hairball!
I was taken as a hostage.
Do you know how disgusting I felt?
That human... perhaps did he
do something weird to you?
How scared was I that he might!
Okay. No matter how rough Mr. Kang may have been,
he wasn't as bad as son of a bitch when we lived in Daejon.
I know that. Since I knew that I left you there alone.
Lies. It doesn't matter, what happens to me.
Whether I starve or eat, sleep or wake up
Why did you call me? Why did you call?!
I'm going to go. You can live and eat well yourself.
Did you hear the last words I said to your dad?
Now, we don't have to go to beggar-like men for food.
We don't have to sleep in motels escaping from them.
You can attend school properly too.
This is the last one. There's nowhere else.
There's really no other place?
There isn't.
If we're kicked out of here or run away again, then let me go.
Do you think you'd be able to live without me, you wench?
Let me go. Say that you'll let me go.
Then, I'll be your daughter for now.
Fine, I'll let you go. I'll do that for you.
This time, how beggar-like is that man?
Whatever is it, please say something nice.
You're the elder.
I, with your mother,
had one daughter but it's become two.
I'm not sure ...
What would you like me to do first?
Whatever it is,
I want to try and do it well for you.
If you tell me what you want, I promise I will try within my greatest efforts-
I don't need anything like a promise.
I don't trust things like that.
Don't think of doing anything like a promise, but just let me attend school.
He felt very sad hearing me say that you have not been attending school regularly.
We prepared everything so that you would be able to attend first thing tomorrow.
Hyo Seon is back!
Unni, hi!
♫ It must be you. I can't be without you. ♫
♫ Like this for another day, month or year ♫
♫ I don't mind even if I am hurt. ♫
It's amazing.
Sis, where are you going?
♫  don't mind even if my heart breaks ♫
Don't be like that.
Since I'm already being called trash, I might as well live as trash.
Unni!
Until everything is arranged, don't get the marriage license.
Since I don't know when I'll be kicked out or need to run away, I'm telling you to do it when there's a chance.
Who am I?
When I talk to her, she's a bit weird.
Our Eun Jo... besides her mother,
she has no one else to call.
♫ Even if I live again ♫